God is still saying something.
On the first Sunday of the year, January 3rd,
2016,
Prophet T.B.Joshua revealed a prophetic message
regarding the nation of North Korea.
These were his words.
We have to pray for the President of North
Korea.
That was New Year's Eve, I said it.
I said, just pray for North Korea.
The reason why I am saying it - I am seeing
an arrow from there
and it will affect the world, if not a section
of the world.
An arrow from there.
So, let us live at peace because the war we are fighting already both in Syria and others is still there.
We cannot afford another one again.
It would end the whole world.
The whole world would be in confusion.
Because what I saw - there are some weapons
there the world does not know about.
If they throw that arrow, there will be confusion.
Remember, there is fight everywhere.
Adding this one to the fight, it means there
will be confusion all over the world.